Inventory of the Wednesday Morning Music Club Records 1964-1992
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Wednesday Morning Music Club Records 1964-1992
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 92 W42
152 items.
Records of the Wednesday Morning Music Club, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1964-1992.
Wednesday Morning Music Club.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 152 items, 11/04/1992.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Wednesday Morning Music Club of Williamsburg, Virginia, brings together women interested in music, encourages musical pursuits, and makes contributions of a musical nature to the community.
Scope and Content Information
The records of the Wednesday Morning Music Club, Williamsburg, Virginia, date 1964-1992 and include programs, publicity, yearbooks, presidents notebooks, minutes, scrapbooks, as well as a history of the organization.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Music appreciation.; Women--Societies and clubs--Virginia- -Williamsburg.; White Women-- Virginia--Societies and clubs.
Geographical name:
Williamsburg (Va.)--Social life and customs--20th century.
Contents List
- Yearbooks, 1985-1992. (Box-folder 1:1)
- Yearbooks, 1975-1985. (Box-folder 1:2)
- Yearbooks, 1965-1975. (Box-folder 1:3)
- Programs, 1976-1990. (Box-folder 1:4)
  Contains programs for the following dates: November 21, 1976; June 14, 1981; March 13, 1983; May 8, 1983; April 18, 1987; April 25, 1988; April 26, 1989; April 19, 1990.
- Publicity, Releases of newspapers, Biographies of performing artists and Interlochen Winners, 1986-1991. (Box-folder 1:5)
- Trip to Winterthur, 20 May, 1986. (Box-folder 1:6)
- History of the Wednesday Morning Music Club, 1980. (Box-folder 1:7)
  History, a 15th anniversary publication of the history of the Wednesday Morning Music Club.
- President's Book, 1985-1988., MsV. 1. (Box 2)
- President's Book, 1985-1990., MsV. 2. (Box 2)
- Meeting Minutes, 1978-1985., MsV. 3. (Box 2)
- Meeting Minutes, 1978-1985., MCV. 4. (Box 2)
- Scrapbook, 1971-1979., MsV. 5. (Box 2)
- Scrapbook, 1973-1984., MCV. 6 (Box 3)
- Scrapbook, 1984-1985., MCV. 7. (Box 3)
- Scrapbook, 1964-1981., MCV. 8 (Box 3)